Toggle navigation [FrankerFaceZ](https://www.frankerfacez.com/)

    * Log In to see Channels

Privacy Policy
==============

Overview
--------

This is the privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") that governs how we, FrankerFaceZ ("FrankerFaceZ", "FFZ", "we", "our" or "us"), use Personal Information (defined below) that we collect, receive and store about individuals in connection with the use of: (i) the website FrankerFaceZ.com, and any other website that we operate (each, together with its sub-domains, content and services, a "Site"); and (ii) the FrankerFaceZ browser extension, and any other software application that we license (each individually, and collectively, the "App"). The Site and the App are individually and collectively referred to herein as the "Services". We do not ourselves host any of the Services – all hosting is done by third party service providers that we engage. This means that data you provide us or that we collect from you (including any Personal Information, as defined below) – as further described in this Privacy Policy – is hosted with such third party service providers on servers that they own or control. Regardless of where such third party service providers are located (and some are located in the US), their servers may be located anywhere in the world (including the US). Your data may even be replicated across multiple servers located in multiple countries. So please be aware that you are consenting to your data being transferred to various third party service providers around the world (including the US).

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://frankerfacez.com/terms.

Information Collection And Use
------------------------------

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

### Usage Data

We may collect information how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

### Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

* Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
* Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
* Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

### Twitch Account Data

To provide our Service to you, we collect some information from your user account on https://twitch.tv ("Twitch").

When signing into FrankerFaceZ via your Twitch account, or by using the FrankerFaceZ extension on Twitch, we collect the following data about your Twitch account, provided to us by Twitch:

* Twitch account user ID and user-name, used for tying your FFZ account to Twitch.
* Twitch oauth token, for communicating with Twitch's API in the context of the user.
* Email address associated with Twitch account, which can be used to opt into email notifications regarding your FrankerFaceZ account, or other FrankerFaceZ features.

### Socket Server Data

When using the FrankerFaceZ extension on Twitch, a connection is made between your browser and FrankerFaceZ servers in order to provide your Twitch session the data needed for FrankerFaceZ to work.

When using the FrankerFaceZ extension on Twitch, the following data may be sent through the socket connection:

* Clients are all assigned a random UUID to identify them. This value is not stored on the server. The client IDs are used to estimate the number of simultaneous users we have connected at any given time.
* Clients send the username and Twitch ID of the logged in Twitch user when connecting. This information is needed for certain features of the FrankerFaceZ extension to work.
* Clients communicate with our server the Twitch channels they are currently active on, so that they can receive relevant data about the channel from us.
* When an error happens in the official FrankerFaceZ client, the error is reported to https://sentry.io ("Sentry"). Error reports can be disabled in settings. They include the error that happened, the page the user was viewing, the user's active settings, the user's active FFZ and Twitch experiments, and a series of recent activity logs that make it easier to understand what was happening when the error occurred. Optionally, users can decide to include their Twitch ID and username with error reports.

Use of Data
-----------

FrankerFaceZ uses the collected data for various purposes:

* To provide and maintain the Service
* To notify you about changes to our Service
* To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
* To provide customer care and support
* To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service
* To monitor the usage of the Service
* To detect, prevent and address technical issues

Transfer of Data
----------------

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

FrankerFaceZ will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

Disclosure Of Data
------------------

### Legal Requirements

FrankerFaceZ may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* To comply with a legal obligation
* To protect and defend the rights or property of FrankerFaceZ
* To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
* To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
* To protect against legal liability

Security Of Data
----------------

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Service Providers
-----------------

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

* **Google Analytics**
    
    Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
    
    You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.
    
    For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

### Link Metadata

Our Service may use third-party Service Providers to fetch and display information about links to other sites displayed on our website or by our official client. Unless otherwise stated, no third-party service receives any personal information other than the URL of the link in question.

* **Discord**
    
    We may use Discord's API to display information about Discord invite links. When viewing this information, clients may directly request thumbnail images from Discord's servers and as such send Discord personal information including the user's IP address.
    
    For more information on Discord, please visit their [Terms of Service](https://discord.com/terms) or view their [Privacy Policy](https://discord.com/privacy).
    
* **Imgur**
    
    We may use Imgur's API to display information about Imgur image links. When viewing this information, clients may directly request thumbnail images from Imgur's servers and as such send Imgur personal information including the user's IP address.
    
    For more information on Imgur, please visit their [Terms of Service](https://imgur.com/tos) or view their [Privacy Policy](https://imgur.com/privacy).
    
* **Twitter**
    
    We may use Twitter's API to display information about Twitter links. When viewing this information, clients may directly request images or videos from Twitter's servers and as such send Twitter personal information including the user's IP address.
    
    For more information on Twitter, please visit their [Terms of Service](https://twitter.com/en/tos) or view their [Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy).
    
* **YouTube**
    
    We may use YouTube's API to display information about links to YouTube's website. When viewing this information, clients may directly request thumbnail images from YouTube's servers and as such send YouTube personal information including the user's IP address.
    
    For more information on YouTube, please visit their [Terms of Service](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms) or view [Google's Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).
    
* **Other Websites**
    
    Our service may use industry standards to fetch information from other websites for display with links to those websites. For a more up-to-date list of supported websites, please view our client's [Policies document](https://github.com/FrankerFaceZ/FrankerFaceZ/blob/master/src/modules/main_menu/legal.md) on GitHub or by navigating to Home > Policies in the official client's Control Center.

Links To Other Sites
--------------------

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Children's Privacy
------------------

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

Changes To This Privacy Policy
------------------------------

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by visiting this page on our website: https://www.frankerfacez.com/contact

© 2023 Dan Salvato LLC - [Contact](https://www.frankerfacez.com/contact) - [Developers](https://api.frankerfacez.com/docs/) - [Discord](https://discord.gg/UrAkGhT) - [GitHub](https://github.com/FrankerFaceZ) - [Privacy Policy](https://www.frankerfacez.com/privacy) - [Terms](https://www.frankerfacez.com/terms)
